Guide to the Ricardo Sánchez Papers, 1941-1995
Department of Special Collections
- SERIES IV: Subject Files.
  - Subseries #1. General files
    - Centro Cultural Aztlán - invitations, press releases, programs, pay stubs (1983 - 1990) (Box 55, Folder 19)
    - Centro Cultural Aztlán - Creative Writing Course (1987) (Box 55, Folder 20)
    - Cervantino: IX Festival International - Encuentro del Poetas (1986) (Box 55, Folder 21)
    - Chavez, Denise (1980) (Box 55, Folder 22)
    - Chiago, Robert Keams - resume (n.d.) (Box 55, Folder 23)
    - "Chicano Art: Resistance and Affirmation, 1965 - 1985" [exhibit] (1992) (Box 55, Folder 24)
      National Museum of American Art
    - Chicano and Latino Issues, miscellaneous: Activism, Incidents, and Politics (Box 55, Folder 25)
      Immigration issues (illegals); Ricardo Falcon; Ricardo Aldape Guerra; Familia Alcantar; Ramon Chacon; Pancho Aguila; Fernando Piñon; Council on Hemispheric Affairs; farm workers -labor; Los Tres Chicanos Unidos ;Jose Angel Gutierrez; Padre Luis Olivares; police brutality; FBI (Federal Bureau of Investigation); Canada; Juarez -Lincoln fire bombing
    - Chicano and Latino Issues, miscellaneous: Activism, Incidents, and Politics, clippings from El Paso Herald Post by Bob Ybarra (Box 55, Folder 26)
    - Chicano and Latino Issues, miscellaneous: Arts (Box 55, Folder 27)
      Emilio Delgado (Sesame Street); LULAC -Jose Garcia de Lara, Ramon Vasquez y Sánchez; murals, Leo Tanguma, Jacinto Quirarte, Felix Fraga ballet folklorico; Ildefonso "Sunny" Ozuna; Jose "Dr. Loco" Cuellar; Miguel Piñero; photography; Washington State University; Felipe de Ortego y Gasca; Mago Orona Gandar; Willie Varela ;James Aguirre
    - Chicano and Latino Issues, miscellaneous: Culture and Identity (Box 55, Folder 28)
      Joe Quintana; Joe Olvera; economics; Felipe de Ortego y Gasca; Washington State University Semana de la Raza ;Mexican First Lady Carmen Romano de Lopez Portillo; Jose Antonio Burciaga
    - Chicano and Latino Issues, miscellaneous: Education (Box 56, Folder 1)
      University of Utah LULAC, Carlos Guerra; Salt Lake City schools ;San Antonio; El Paso; Eastern Washington University; Chicano Teachers of English, Carlota Cardenas de Dwyer
    - Chicano and Latino Issues, miscellaneous: Literature (Box 56, Folder 2)
      Sandra Cisneros; Joe Olvera; Portillo Trambley
    - "Chicano - Latino Art; Images in the Age of AIDS" [exhibit] (1992) (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Chicano and Latino demographics (1978) (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Chicano Lite and Power, Inc. (1975 - 1976) (Box 56, Folder 5)
      including correspondence from "Bertha"
    - Chicano Cultural Distribution Center (1975) (Box 56, Folder 6)
      including proposal by Sánchez
    - Chicano Mass Communications Sensitivity Training Committee (1972) (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Chicano Training Center, Inc. (1974) (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Chicanos por la Causa (1969) (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Chicanos Unidos for Action (1976) (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Church of the United Community (1988) (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Cisneros, Henry (1987-1988) (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - CLETA UNAM (1987) (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Coca-Cola (1980s) (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - College Knowledge for the Mind (1992 - 1993) (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Colorado Coalition in Support of the Chicano Liberation Struggle (n.d.) (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Colorado Council on Migrant and Seasonal Agricultural Workers and Families - "Community Life Handbook and Resource Manual for Educational Field Personnel" pp. 1 - 113 (1970) (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Colorado Council on Migrant and Seasonal Agricultural Workers and Families - "Community Life Handbook and Resource Manual for Educational Field Personnel" pp. 114 - 198 (1970) (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - Colorado Council on Migrant and Seasonal Agricultural Workers and Families - Interstate Itinerant Migrant Health Project (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Colorado Council on Migrant and Seasonal Agricultural Workers and Families - I.N.P. Proposal (1972?) (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Colorado Council on Migrant and Seasonal Agricultural Workers and Families - office files (1970) (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - Colorado Council on Migrant and Seasonal Agricultural Workers and Families - office files (1970) (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Colorado Council on Migrant and Seasonal Agricultural Workers and Families - office files (1970 - 1971) (Box 57, Folder 2.1)
    - Columbia Basin College - Young Writers Competition (1992) (Box 57, Folder 2.2)
    - Columbia University Graduate School of Journalism - Summer Program in Broadcast and Print Journalism (1989) (Box 57, Folder 2.3)
    - Comite Chicano Mexicano Nacional de Apoyo Al E.Z.L.N. (Ejercito Zapatisto de Liberación Nacional) (1994) (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Commission for Mexican-American Affairs (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Committee for the Defense of Muñiz and Justice (1983) (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Committee for the Development of Mass Communications - Doubleday Broadcasting Co., Federal Communications Commission (1972 - 1973) (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Community Action on Latin America (1977) (Box 57, Folder 7)
      sterilization
    - La Comunidad de Sur El Paso (n.d.) (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - CON SAFO (1975) (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Conal, Robbie (1988) (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Conejos County, Colorado (n.d.) (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Crossroads Urban Center - The Crossroads Advocate (1977) (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Culture Clash (1988) (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - De León, Aidé - Canto Aidé (1985) (Box 57, Folder 14.1)
    - De Leon, Luis Diaz - resume (n.d.) (Box 57, Folder 14.2)
    - De León, Nephtalí (1977 - 1992) (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - del Castillo, Moises Espino (1982 - 1986) (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - Delgado, Abelardo (1971 - 1991) (Box 57, Folder 17)
      includes various poems and articles
    - Delgado, Abelardo - "News Items on Chicanos..." ( 1977) (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - Delgado, Abelardo - "News Items on Chicanos..." ( 1977) (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - Delgado, Abelardo - "News items on Chicanos..." [photocopy] ( 1977) (Box 57, Folder 20)
      for preservation purposes, please use this copy for research unless originals are specifically required
    - Diocese of El Paso, Texas Centennial Celebration (1936) (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - Dobie - Paisano Fellowships(1975) (Box 57, Folder 22)
    - Duran, Phillip H. - Case Against University of Texas at El Paso, sections 2-10 (1970 - 1976) (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Duran, Phillip H. - Case Against Washington State Univ. - "Incident Chronology" (1990) (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Duran, Phillip H. - Case Against Washington State Univ. - "Incident Chronology" Appendixes A1 - A20 (1990) (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Duran, Phillip H. - Case Against Washington State University - "Incident Chronology" Appendix A21 (1990 - 1992) (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Duran, Phillip H. - Case Against Washington State Univ. - "Incident Chronology" Appendixes B1 - B8 (1988-1989) (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Duran, Phillip H. - Case Against Washington State Univ. - "Incident Chronology" Appendixes B9 - B10 (1971 -1989) (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Duran, Phillip H. - Case Against Washington State Univ. - "My WSU Story" (1989) (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Duran, Phillip H. - Case Against Washington State Univ. - "Notes" (1986 - 1991) (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Duran, Phillip H. - Case Against Washington State Univ. - OFCCP Complaint Appeal Supplement (1991) (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Duran, Phillip H. - Case Against Washington State Univ. - Writings and grievance documentation (1991 - 1994) (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - El Paso: Arts, Tourism and Miscellaneous (Box 59, Folder 1)
      Art Lewis
    - El Paso Community College (EPCC) - student papers (1976) (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - El Paso Community College (EPCC) - teaching materials (1989-1990) (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - El Paso Council on Alcoholism (1971) (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - El Paso County Borderlands Cultural Center (1989) (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - El Paso Independent School District (1972) (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - El Paso Public Library (Chicano Related events and collections) (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Encuentro de Poetas del Mundo Latino (Mexico) (1986) (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - The Encyclopedic Dictionary of Chicano Literature (prospectus) (1978) (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - "English Only" Movement (1984-1988) (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Entelequia clippings, photographs, and publicity (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - La Esperanza, Inc., Jose Rendon (1975) (Box 59, Folder 12)
    - Estrella, Armando, resume (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - Etheridge Knights Festival of Arts (1990-1992) (Box 59, Folder 14)
    - Ethnic Studies (miscellaneous) (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - "Expresiones Hispanas 88/89" (1988) (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - Extension de Servicios y Educacion, Worden, El Paso (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - Falcón, Peter Gonzales (n.d.) (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - La Familia del Paso, Inc. (1988?) (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - Ferrer, Rafael (1982) (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - Festival de Flor y Canto (1973) (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - Festival Floricanto Dos (1975) (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - Festival Floricanto Tres (1976) (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - Festival Floricanto Cuatro (Albuquerque) (1977) (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - Fine Arts Center del Barrio (1975) (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - Flores, Carolina (n.d.) (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - Floridation (1970s) (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - Ford Foundation, "Hispanic Theatre Organization in the United States" (1986) (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - Foundation for Urban and Neighborhood Development (FUND) (1970) (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - Frescas, Lupe, Ballet Folklorico Christo Rey (n.d.) (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - El Fuego Nuevo (1977) (Box 59, Folder 31)
    - Galarza, Ernesto (1987) (Box 59, Folder 32)
    - Garcia, Irma ("La Rosa Negra") (1986) (Box 59, Folder 33)
    - Geese Theatre Company (Box 59, Folder 34)
    - Gonzales, Rodolfo "Corky" (Box 59, Folder 35)
      La Raza Unida Party
    - Gonzalez, Francisco (1980s) (Box 59, Folder 36)
    - Gonzales, Nivia (1984) (Box 59, Folder 37)
    - Gorman, R.C. (1983) (Box 59, Folder 38)
    - Granite School District (Salt Lake City) (1980) (Box 59, Folder 39)
      nutrition
    - Grupo Fusil Anti-Represión, Partido Frente de la Liberación / Ch. L.A. (1974) (Box 59, Folder 40)
    - Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center (1983-1988, n.d.) (Box 59, Folder 41)
    - Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center, clippings (Box 59, Folder 42)
      San Antonio Arts, various issues and artists
    - Guadalupe Cultural Arts Center, Influence: An Exhibition of Works by Contemporary Hispanic Artists Living in San Antonio, Texas (1987) (Box 59, Folder 43)
    - Guadalupe Theatre Project (1981, 1887) (Box 59, Folder 44)
    - Guerrero, El Zarco, clippings (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Guerrero, El Zarco, flyers, brochures (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Guerrero, El Zarco, photgraphs (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - HAMAS (Hispanic Academy of Media Arts and Sciences) (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Health Issues, miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 5)
      mental health Salubridad Chicano: Su Preservación y Mantenimiento -The Chicano Plan for Mental Health (1975) special education nuclear power
    - Hispanic American Development Program (Springfield, MA) (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Hispanic Organization of Latin Actors (HOLA) - La Nueva Ola (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - "Ideological Analysis" (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Independent Publishing Fund of the Americas (1977) (Box 60, Folder 9.1)
    - Indictment of the Federal Government of the United States of America (Box 60, Folder 9.2)
    - Instituto Cultural Mexicano - various exhibits and performances (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Interagency Resource and Information Center (1974) (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - International Conference on Penal Abolition (ICOPA) (1987-1991) (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - International Emergency Committee to defend the life of Abimael Guzman (1993) (Box 60, Folder 13)
    - International Mariachi Festival (1986) (Box 60, Folder 14)
    - International Parliament for Safety and Peace (1992) (Box 60, Folder 15)
    - Interstate Congress for Equal Rights and Responsibilities, Inc. (1976) (Box 60, Folder 16)
    - Joint Commission on Correctional Manpower and Training, Inc., Seminar (1968) (Box 60, Folder 17)
    - Joint Strategy and Action Committee, Inc. (1985) (Box 60, Folder 18)
    - Juneteenth (1981) (Box 60, Folder 19)
    - Kansas Advisory Committee on Mexican-American Affairs (1981) (Box 60, Folder 20)
    - Ku Klux Klan (1977) (Box 60, Folder 21)
    - LA Prints: Self-Help Graphics Atelier Program (1983-1986) (Box 60, Folder 22)
    - Latin American Development Society (LADS) (Box 60, Folder 23)
    - Latin American issues, miscellaneous (Box 60, Folder 24)
    - La Savage, Vanessa (n.d.) (Box 61, Folder 1)
      Ervil Morel LeBaron McDonald
    - legal documents translated by Sánchez (1972-1973) (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Le Roy, Lewis (1984) (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Lewis, Rob (n.d.) (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Liberación Learning Center - Pedagogy of the Oppressed (1975) (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Literary Journals, miscellaneous (calls for submissions, etc) (Box 61, Folder 6)
      De Colores Café Solo Santo Niño
    - Literature (non-Chicano) miscellaneous (Texas) (Box 61, Folder 7)
      R.G. Vliet ;David Lindsey; Rosemary Catacalos; Bryce Milligan ;Arthur Munoz Dave Oliphant; Robert Bonazzi; Paul Christensen; David Reidel; Vassar Miller; William Barney; William Burford; Claude Stanush ;Morris Morrison
    - La Llamada Publicaciones (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Los Angeles Police - Chicano Issues (1971) (Box 61, Folder 9)
      Eustacio "Frank" Martinez ;Los Tres del Barrio
    - LUChA (League of United Chicano Artists) (Austin) (1979-1982) (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - LULAC (League of Latin American Citizens) - Comite Revolucionario Ricardo Falcon (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - MACHOS (Box 61, Folder 12)
      Wyoming Inmate Chicano Club
    - Magazines of Mexico (Box 61, Folder 13)
    - "A Major Museum of Hispanic Arts" (Box 61, Folder 14)
    - "Maquiladoras in Juárez" (n.d.) (Box 61, Folder 15)
    - Marin, Richard "Cheech" (Box 61, Folder 16)
    - Hector Marroquín Defense Committee (1978) (Box 61, Folder 17)
    - Martin University (1992) (Box 61, Folder 18)
    - Martinez, Ernesto (1973-1975, n.d.) (Box 61, Folder 19)
    - Martinez, Francisco "Kiko" (1981-1986, n.d.) (Box 61, Folder 20)
    - Martinez, Jose Antonio - The Honorable Pedro Sánchez (Box 61, Folder 21)
    - MEChA (Movimiento Estudantil Chicano de Aztlán), "Los Olvidados" (1974) (Box 61, Folder 22)
    - MEChA (Movimiento Estudantil Chicano de Aztlán) (1976) (Box 61, Folder 23)
    - MEChA (Movimiento Estudantil Chicano de Aztlán) (1991, n.d.) (Box 61, Folder 24)
    - MEChA (Movimiento Estudantil Chicano de Aztlán) (n.d.) (Box 61, Folder 25)
    - Medlock Southwest Management Corporation (Box 61, Folder 26)
    - Medrano Family (1970) (Box 61, Folder 27)
    - Mercy Alliance of Prison Ministries (1988) (Box 61, Folder 28)
    - Mexican American Affairs Conference, Preliminary Report (El Paso) (1973) (Box 61, Folder 29)
    - Mexican American Youth Organization (MAYO) (n.d.) (Box 61, Folder 30)
    - Mexican Folk Art at San Antonio Museum of Art (1986) (Box 61, Folder 31)
      Con Cariño exhibit
    - MexicArte: Dia de los Muertos (1984) (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - "Mexico: The New Generations" (n.d.) (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - "Mexico: Splendors of 30 Generations" - San Antonio Museum of Art (1991) (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Meyer, Steven E. (1983) (Box 61, Folder 35)
      Rainow Research, Inc.
    - Minneapolis 72 (1972) (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Minnesota Citizens' Review Commission of the FBI (1977) (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Minority Human Service Training Program (Salt Lake City) (n.d.) (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - "Minority Arts: A New Direction" (1985) (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Minority Issues, miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 3)
      African American -black issues Federal Bureau of Investigation (FBI)
    - Minority Writers Conference on Television Production (1980) (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Missal (n.d.) (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Montalvo, Jose (Box 62, Folder 6)
      Ramon Vasquez y Sánchez, Centro Cultural Aztlan
    - Montalvo, Roel (1976) (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Muriedas, Ramon (Box 62, Folder 8)
      photographs and brochure
    - National Arts Society of Pass Christian, MS (1991) (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - National Association for Chicano Studies (NACS) (1978-1993) (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - National Association for Chicano Studies (NACS), Northwest Region (1993) (Box 62, Folder 11.1)
    - National Association for Chicano Studies (NACS), Northwest Region, WSU Conference (1993) (Box 62, Folder 11.2)
    - National Association of Third World Writers (1980) (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - National Center for Audio Experimentation (1973) (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - National Chicano Moratorium (1980, 1990, 1992) (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - National Coalition for Police Accountability (1991) (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - National Council for Chicano Sociolinguistic Research, Proceedings (1974) (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - National Endowment for the Arts, miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - National Exploratory Conference on Chicano Sociolinguistics (1974) (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - National Geographic Society (1976) (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - National Hispanic Institute, miscellaneous (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - National Hispanic Institute, ATENEO (1982) (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - National Hispanic Institute, Lorenzo de Zavala Mock Legislative Session (1982) (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - National Hispanic Media Coalition (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - National Hispanic Theatre Conference, imcluding notes by Sánchez (1986) (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - National Interreligious Task Force on Criminal Justice (NITFCJ) - Reflections on Twenty-Five Years... (1993) (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - National Interreligious Task Force on Criminal Justice (NITFCJ) (1977-1979) (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - National Interreligious Task Force on Criminal Justice (NITFCJ) (1980-1986) (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - National Interreligious Task Force on Criminal Justice (NITFCJ) (1987-1989) (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - National Interreligious Task Force on Criminal Justice (NITFCJ) (1990-1993) (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - National Latino Media Coalition, including speech by Sánchez (1973) (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - National Movement of La Raza (1991) (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - National Public Radio (1981) (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - National Urban Coalition (1973) (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Native American Issues, miscellaneous (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Navajo Community College (1975) (Box 63, Folder 11)
      student autobiographies
    - Navajo Community College (1976) (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Navarro, Joe, University of Utah (1981) (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - New Mexico State University (1972-1973) (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - New Mexico State University (1973-1975) (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Nickerson, Sheila (n.d.) (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Nielsen, Ron (1989) (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Noel Therapeutic Center Halfway House (1981) (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - North American Congress on Latin America (NACLA) (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Nosotros - Carlos Santana benefit concert (1987) (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Nosotros Theatre Organization news magazine (1987-1988) (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Onda Magazín (1983) (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - "One City -- Many Cultures..." (San Antonio) (1981) (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - One World Poetry (P78) (1978) (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - One World Poetry (P79) (1979) (Box 64, Folder 6)
      mementoes and related miscellaneous
    - Operation "We Care" (Our Lady's Youth Center, El Paso - Reverend Richard Thomas) (1971) (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Open Dialogue II (San Antonio) (1985) (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Open Dialogue II, bio forms and photos of participants (Box 64, Folder 9)
      Maxine F. Brown Salli M. K. Benedict Simon Brascoupé Juan M. Carillo Clayborne Chavers E'Vonne Coleman Rorie Carmen De Novais Amina J. Dickerson Jonathan Katz Dai Sil Kim-Gibson Ronne Hartfield George Charles Koch Robert Lee Uenice J. Lockhart-Moss Jo Long Robert L. Lynch Sharon Maeda Amelita Mandingo Milton C. Morris Jacinto Quirarte Joe B. Rodriguez Luis J. Rodriguez Delisa Kay Saunders John E. Skuce A. B. Spellman Warren K. Summers Sally Palmer Thomason Robin Tryloff Donald Woods Luis Valdez Jack Wright Curtis King Jane Delgado Jennifer Lawson Edward J. Pfister
    - Open Dialogue III (1988) (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Orona Gandara, Mago (1977-1990) (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Ortiz Monasterio, Luis (1986) (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Pajarito Publications (Box 64, Folder 13)
      De Colores
    - The Pan American Round Table of Edinburg, Texas (1988-1989) (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Papeles de la Frontera (San Diego State University) (1976) (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Paperbacks... y más - Poets of Tejas, clippings (Box 64, Folder 16)
      various poets and events
    - Paperbacks... y más - Poets of Tejas, financial papers (1983-1985) (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Paperbacks... y más - Poets of Tejas, workshop participants (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Paperbacks... y más - Poets of Tejas, books, orders, business trips (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Paperbacks... y más - Poets of Tejas, information about speakers (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Paperbacks... y más - Poets of Tejas, gift certificates (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Paperbacks... y más - Poets of Tejas, publicity fliers, mailers, etc. (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Paperbacks... y más - Poets of Tejas, press releases (1984-1986) (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Paperbacks... y más - Poets of Tejas, press releases (1987-1992, n.d.) (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Paperbacks... y más - Poets of Tejas, correspondence (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Pena, Frederico (1983) (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - People of Color Task Force on Criminal Justice - Colorations Newsletter (1985, n.d.) (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Nacho Perez Defense Committee (n.d.) (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Piñero, Miguel (n.d.) (Box 65, Folder 8)
      Arte Público Press Revista Chicano-Riqueña Nicolás Kanellos, publisher
    - Los Pobres Bilingual Theatre Repertory Company (1974-1975) (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Political Issues, miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 10)
      Police Brutality; abortion; Pope John Paul II
    - Presbyterian Criminal Justice Program (1973-1991) (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Prison Art, miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 12)
      pañuelo (handkerchief) art
    - Prison Issues, miscellaneous (Box 65, Folder 13)
      death penalty Coalition for Prisoners' Rights The Prisoner
    - Prisoners Defense Committee (1986) (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Prisoners Defense Committee (1984-1986, n.d.) (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Prisoners Defense Committee (San Antonio) (1973-1983) (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Project HELP (Anthony, NM) (1971) (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Proposals and Applications: Arts Council of San Antonio, grant application (1986) (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Proposals and Applications: City of El Paso Arts Resource Department Direct Funding Program (n.d.) (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Proposals and Applications: Corporation for Public Broadcasting, "Pinto" proposal (1981) (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Proposals and Applications: El Paso Independent School District, Project TREND proposal (n.d.) (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Proposals and Applications: National Endowment for the Arts (1973-1993) (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Proposals and Applications: National Hispanic Institute: project HEARTH proposal (n.d.) (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Proposals and Applications: National Puerto Rican Policy Network (1982) (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Proposals and Applications: Paisano Grant Application (1986) (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Proposals and Applications: Presbyterian Church, cultural distribution center proposal (1975) (Box 66, Folder 1)